let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What’s the name of Joey’s penguin?",
    answer: "Hugsy",
    options: [
      "Snowflake",
      "Waddle",
      "Hugsy",
      "Bobber"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is Chandler’s middle name?",
    answer: "Muriel",
    options: [
      "Muriel",
      "Jason",
      "Kim",
      "Zachary"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What kind of uniform does Joey wear to Monica and Chandler’s wedding?",
    answer: "Soldier",
    options: [
      "Chef",
      "Soldier",
      "Fire Fighter",
      "A baseball player"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Monica and Chandler met on Thanksgiving in 1987. She pursued her career as a chef because Chandler complimented her on which dish?",
    answer: "Mac and cheese",
    options: [
      "Green bean casserole",
      "Meatloaf",
      "Stuffing",
      "Mac and cheese"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many sisters does Joey have ?",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "7",
      "5",
      "2",
      "None"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What song does Ross’ monkey, Marcel, keep playing?",
    answer: "‘The Lion Sleeps Tonight‘ by The Tokens",
    options: [
      "‘The Lion Sleeps Tonight‘ by The Tokens",
      "‘Tiny Dancer’ by Elton John ",
      "‘The Way You Looked Tonight’ by Tony Bennett",
      "‘Careless Whisper’ by George Michael"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What does Chandler have to do to get Joey to forgive him, after having kissed Cathy?",
    answer: "Lie in a wooden box for six hours",
    options: [
    "Wear blue lipstick",
    "Lie in a wooden box for six hours",
    "Furnish their apartment",
    "Move to Yemen"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the ‘Gellar Cup’ made of?",
    answer: "A troll doll nailed to a two by four",
    options: [
      "A 3D woman coming out of a photo frame",
      "A troll doll nailed to a two by four",
      "A fruit bowl found in the garbage",
      "A sock puppet shaped like a bunny"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the name of the hairless cat Rachel gets for herself?",
    answer: "Mrs Whiskerson",
    options: [
      "Fluffy",
      "Mrs Whiskerson",
      "Chi Chi",
      "Mozzarella"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the next line in the song, “Monica, Monica, have a happy Hanukkah”",
    answer: "“Saw Santa Claus, he said hello to Ross”",
    options: [
    "“And please tell Joey, Christmas will be snowy”",
    "“Saw Santa Claus, he said hello to Ross”",
    "“Spin the dreidel, Rachel”",
    "“Went to the store, sat on Santa’s lap”"

    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What ridiculously expensive gift did Ross get Carol when he fell in love with her?",
    answer: "A crystal duck",
    options: [
      "A shop window brooch",
      "A crystal duck",
      "An early edition of her favourite book",
      "A $500 dollar watch"
    ]
  },
   {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Now imagine you live at the supermarket. Who said this ?",
    answer: "Chandler",
    options: [
      "Chandler",
      "Ross",
      "Gunther",
      "Nora Bing"
    ]
  }
  
];